Guide to the Records of Director of Academic Program Review, Barnett Hamberger 1972-2003 RG 9.7 RG 9.7
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Graduate Commission, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 2, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 1 of 2, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Commission- Folder 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Commission (cont'd), 1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Manhattanville, 1985, 1986, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - NYU General Education, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - State Education Department, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - State Education Department, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - State Education Department, 1981 June-August (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - State Education Department, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - State Education Department, 1980 June-August (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - State Education Department- Folder 1 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - State Education Department- Folder 2 of 2, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - State Education Department, 1979 June-August (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - State Education Department- Folder 1 of 2, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - State Education Department- Folder 2 of 2, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - State Inventory of Registered Programs, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Statistics Book, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - 1983 Summer Session Opinion Survey- Folder 1 of 2, 1981, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - 1983 Summer Session Opinion Survey- Folder 2 of 2, 1981, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Summer Session Committee- Folder 1 of 2, 1975, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Summer Session Committee- Folder 2 of 2, 1975, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - NYU High School Summer Program Interest Questionnaire, 1990, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225560 7
  - Coles Review Group #1, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Coles Review Group #2- Folder 1 of 2, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Coles Review Group #2- Folder 2 of 2, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Coles Review Group #3- Folder 1 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Coles Review Group #3- Folder 2 of 2, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Coles De Capriles Room Dedication- Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1982, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Coles De Capriles Room Dedication- Folder 2 of 2, 1981-1982, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Coles Center SCE Courses, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Coles Hall of Fame, 1981-1982, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Coles Dedication, 1981, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Coles- Folder 1 of 4, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Coles- Folder 2 of 4, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Coles- Folder 3 of 4, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Coles- Folder 4 of 4, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Coles- Folder 1 of 4, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Coles- Folder 2 of 4, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Coles- Folder 3 of 4, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Coles- Folder 4 of 4, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Coles, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Coles Restricted Account--Folder 1 of 4, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Coles Restricted Account--Folder 2 of 4, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Coles Restricted Account--Folder 3 of 4, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Coles Restricted Account--Folder 4 of 4, 1981-1985 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Coles Center, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Coles Center Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225552 4
  - Coles Center Budget--Folder 1 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Coles Center Budget--Folder 2 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Coles Center Budget--Folder 3 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Coles Center--Folder 1 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Coles Center--Folder 2 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Coles Center--Folder 3 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Coles Center--Folder 4 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Coles Center--Folder 1 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Coles Center--Folder 2 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Coles Center--Folder 3 of 3, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Coles Budget--Folder 1 of 3, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Coles Budget--Folder 2 of 3 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Coles Budget--Folder 3 of 3, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Coles Pro Shop Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Coles Pro Shop/Mail Order, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Coles Pro Shop Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Coles Budget--Folder 1 of 3, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Coles Budget--Folder 2 of 3, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Coles Budget--Folder 3 of 3, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Coles Capital Campaign, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Community Board-NYU Committee on Coles, 198301984 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Community Board-NYU Committee on Coles, 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Community Board-NYU Committee on Coles--Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Community Board-NYU Committee on Coles--Folder 2 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Community Board-NYU Committee on Coles, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Membership Rules Requests, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Coles/School of Continuing Ed., 1982-1983 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Violets Booster Club--Folder 1 of 4, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Violets Booster Club--Folder 2 of 4, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Violets Booster Club--Folder 3 of 4, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Violets Booster Club--Folder 4 of 4, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Violets Booster Club--Folder 1 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Violets Booster Club--Folder 2 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Violets Booster Club, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 1 of 3, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 2 of 3, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 3 of 3, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 1 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    3 1142 04225561 5
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 2 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 3 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Recruitment--Folder 1 of 3, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Recruitment--Folder 2 of 3, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Recruitment--Folder 3 of 3, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Recruitment--Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Recruitment--Folder 2 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Recruitment, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Recruitment, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Recruitment, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Budget--Folder 1 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Budget--Folder 2 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Academic Standards, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Athletic Academic Awards, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Basketball--Folder 1 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Basketball--Folder 2 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Basketball--Folder 3 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Academics, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Academic Standards Subcommittee--Folder 1 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Academic Standards Subcommittee--Folder 2 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 2 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 1 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 2 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 3 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 4 of 4, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 1 of 5, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    3 1142 04225559 9
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 2 of 5, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 3 of 5, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 4 of 5, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics--Folder 5 of 5, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Basketball--Folder 1 of 4, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Basketball--Folder 2 of 4, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Basketball--Folder 3 of 4, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Basketball--Folder 4 of 4, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Opening Basketball Game--Folder 1 of 4, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Opening Basketball Game--Folder 2 of 4, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Opening Basketball Game--Folder 3 of 4, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Opening Basketball Game--Folder 4 of 4, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Athletic Achievement Awards--Folder 1 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Athletic Achievement Awards--Folder 2 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - NCAA Surveys--Folder 1 of 6, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - NCAA Surveys--Folder 2 of 6, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - NCAA Surveys--Folder 3 of 6, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - NCAA Surveys--Folder 4 of 6, 1986=1987 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - NCAA Surveys--Folder 5 of 6, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - NCAA Surveys--Folder 6 of 6, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Athletics Cable TV, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - University Athletic Association--Folder 1 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - University Athletic Association--Folder 2 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - University Athletic Association--Folder 3 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - News Stories on Formation of UAA--Folder 1 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - News Stories on Formation of UAA--Folder 2 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - News Stories on Formation of UAA--Folder 3 of 3, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Report--Drafts, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    3 1142 04058785 2
  - Coles Advisory Board--Folder 1 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Coles Advisory Board--Folder 2 of 2, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Intercollegiate Advisory Committee--Folder 1 of 3, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Intercollegiate Advisory Committee--Folder 2 of 3, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Intercollegiate Advisory Committee--Folder 3 of 3, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Coles Advisory Board--Folder 1 of 3, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Coles Advisory Board--Folder 2 of 3, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Coles Advisory Board--Folder 3 of 3, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Coles Advisory Board--Folder 1 of 2, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Coles Advisory Board--Folder 2 of 2, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Athletic Cable TV Contract Drafts, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Budget--Folder 1 of 2, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Budget--Folder 1 of 2, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Intercollege Athletics Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Restricted Account Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Restricted Account Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Intercollegiate Budget--Folder 1 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Intercollegiate Budget--Folder 2 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Report, 1981-1982 (Box 26b, Folder 1)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Cable TV, 1983-1984 (Box 26b, Folder 2)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Report, 1981-1982 (Box 26b, Folder 3)
  - Eligibility, 1985-1986 (Box 26b, Folder 4)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics, 1980-1981 (Box 26b, Folder 5)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Basketball Attendance, 1985-1986 (Box 26b, Folder 6)
  - Int. Ath. Report Background, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058784 5
  - Athletic Academic Awards, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - UAA Press Conf., 1986 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Advisory Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Ath. Standards Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Violet Booster Club, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - UAA, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - UAA, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - UAA Summer, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Tishman Endowment Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - NCAA Surveys, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - NCAA, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - UAA Delegates Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Athletic Recruitment, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - VBC Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058788 6
  - UAA Schedules, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - UAA, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - UAA, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Tishman Endowment Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Basketball Away Reception, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - UAA Pres. Comm., 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Study in Women's Basketball, undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Restricted Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - UAA Constitution, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - UAA Constitution, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Basketball Attendance, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Basketball Attendance, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Athletics Ruden Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Chase Manhattan Tournament, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Athletics Endowment Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Academics, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Athletics, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Athletic Income Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Athletic Restricted Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Athletic Rosters, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Athletic Rosters, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Coles Pro Shop, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058786 0
  - Hotline, 1985-1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - SCE (Summer), undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Usage, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Alumni, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Alumni, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Alumni, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Alumni, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Board, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Board, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Board, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Plant Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Plant Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Capital Campaign, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Computerization, 1983-1987 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Community, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Community, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Community, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Community, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Restricted Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Restricted Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Restricted Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Center, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Center, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Center, 1986-1987 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Center, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058787 8
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Cable TV, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - NCAA, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - NCAA Audit, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Chase Manhattan Tournament, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Advisory Committee Reports, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Eligibilities, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Basketball Attendance, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Basketball, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Endowment Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Income Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Academics, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Athletics, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Coles Endowment Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Coles Endowment Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Coles Fund Raising, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Coles Recreation, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Coles Winter Celebration, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - AAUP, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225568 0
  - Accreditation (1 of 3), 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Accreditation (2 of 3), 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Accreditation (3 of 3), 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Brademas, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Creative Arts Team, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Community Fund (1 of 4), 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Community Fund (2 of 4), 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Community Fund (3 of 4), 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Community Fund (4 of 4), 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Course Approvals (1 of 2), undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Course Approvals (2 of 2), undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Commission, 1988-1990 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - HEOP, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Middle States, 1986-1992 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Middle States University Conference, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Middle States Off-Campus Activities, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Multinational/Multicultural Education Survey, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - NACUBO Reports, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - National Endowment Grant Planning Committee, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225567 2
  - NYC Marathon, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - NYC Sports Commission, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - NYU Cooper Union, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda to LJO, 1987-1990 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Picnic Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Registration, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Schweitzer Chair, 1985-1989 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - State Education Department, 1982-1990 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Responses to State Education Department, 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - State Education Department General Correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Summer High School Program (1 of 3), 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Summer High School Program (2 of 3), 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Summer High School Program (3 of 3), 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Summer Institute, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Summer Liasion Committee, 1988-1991 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Summer Sessions Study Group, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Summer Sessions Administrative Task Force, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Summer Sessions Subcommittee to Increase Student Participation by NYU Students, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - University Planning Committee, undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - University Production Unit, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - U.S. Education Foundation in India, undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Zoning, undated (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Academic Program Review 1990 Budget (Jan-Dec) (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Athletics Budgets, 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - FIJI Bike-A-Thon, undated (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Athletics Income Budgets (1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225566 4
  - Athletics Income Budgets (2 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Athletics Restricted Budgets (1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Athletics Restricted Budgets (2 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Budgets, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Coles Plant Budgets (1 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Coles Plant Budgets (2 of 2), 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Coles Budgets, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Coles Budgets, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Coles Budgets, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Athletics, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Athletics, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Athletics, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Academics, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Academics, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Athletic Academic Achievement Awards, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Academic Achievement Awards, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Athletic Advisory Board Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Athletic Advisory Board Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Asphalt Green, undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Basketball, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Basketball, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Athletic Basketball Attendance, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Athletic Basketball Attendance, 1988-1990 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Away Basketball Receptions, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225565 6
  - Away Basketball Receptions, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Springfield Hall of Fame, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Men's Coaching Position Applications, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Cable Television, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Degree Compliance Program, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Final Grades, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Graduation Rates, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Health Workshop, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Madison Square Garden Plan, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - N.I.T., undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - N.I.T., undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Athletic News, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Athletic News, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Rudin Foundation, 1988-1991 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Athletic Rudin Foundation, 1988-1991 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Rudin Foundation, 1988-1991 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Athletic Schedules, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Athletic Schedules, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Athletic Stevens Institute, undated (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Student Transcripts, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Student Transcripts, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Student Transcripts, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Student Transcripts, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Athletic Tutors, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Varsity Club, 1985-1990 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Varsity Club, 1985-1990 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - VBC Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - VBC Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Athletic Women's Hall of Fame, undated (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Coles Center, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Coles Center, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Coles Advisory Board Future Review, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225564 9
  - Coles Air Conditioning, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Coles Battery Park City, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Coles Capital Reserve, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Coles Capital Reserve, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Coles Clubs, 1989-1990 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Coles Crew, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Coles Fieldhouse Lighting, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Coles Licensing/International Collegiate Enterprises, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Coles Licensing/International Collegiate Enterprises, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Coles Memberships, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Coles Alumni Memberships, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Coles Alumni Memberships, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Coles Community Memberships, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Coles Pro Shop, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Coles Pro Shop, 1988-1990 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Coles Recreation, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)